Privacy Policy
==============

This Agreement was last modified on March 14, 2018.

* * *

TrackJS LLC ("TrackJS", "we", "us") provides error tracking services ("Services") for web applications. We are committed to protecting the privacy of our customers, and their users. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe our practices in gathering, securing, and using application and personal data.

By making Application Data or Personal Data available to us through our website, Services, or related communication, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and your expressly consent to the processing of your Application Data and Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your Personal Data may be processed outside the country in which it was collected, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

Information We Collect
----------------------

TrackJS may collect and process the following Personal Data from you:

### Data You Give Us

TrackJS collects Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide us with such Data in the course of using our website, Services, or related materials. For example, when you subscribe to our newsletter you volunteer your name and email address.

### Data We Collect Automatically

TrackJS and our service providers collect certain technical information automatically when you visit our website or use our Services, such as your browser, operating system, referrer, IP address, and other Internet data. We gather this information with the use of cookies.

### Data Collected for Business

We may store and collect Personal Data from you when you do business with us, such as storing your Billing Address and contact information so that we may maintain business relations with you as your vendor, supplier, or other third party.

### Data Collected as your Data Processor

TrackJS collects data on behalf of our customers in the context of providing our Services. All data collection provided by the Service is completely controlled by the customer, so you can choose the right level of information collection and privacy for your needs. For example, you can configure the Services to ignore or anonymize IP Addresses from your users should you not want TrackJS to store that data. For more information on configuring the service, see [the Documentation](https://docs.trackjs.com/).

How We Protect Your Information
-------------------------------

TrackJS uses a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your Personal Data. All supplied payment information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (e.g., credit cards) will not be stored on our servers.

TrackJS will never sell your Personal Data to anyone. Your Personal Data is only accessible to TrackJS employees, contractors, and our service providers that require access in order to administer the TrackJS website, services, or related materials, or to provide you with support and assistance.

How We Use Your Information
---------------------------

Personal Data we collect from you is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. TrackJS uses your Personal Data in the following ways:

* To create and secure your account on our network,
* To identify you as a user in our system,
* To provide improved administration of our website, Services, and related materials,
* To improve the quality of experience when you interact with our website, Services, and related materials,
* To send you welcome, setup, and notification emails in relation to providing the TrackJS Services,
* To solicit your feedback on our Services.

Cookies
-------

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. We use cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. TrackJS visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the TrackJS website, Service, or other materials. Certain features may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Privacy Policy Changes
----------------------

Although changes are likely to be minor, TrackJS may change our Privacy Policy from time to time, at our sole discretion. TrackJS encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
